Guide to the Socialist Party (U.S.) Correspondence TAM.056.009
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- SERIES II: STATE CORRESPONDENCE
  - Massachusetts, Feb 1914-Nov 1935 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:39
  - Michigan, Mar 1905 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:40
  - New Hampshire, Jan 1916-Mar 1923 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:41
  - New Jersey, 1902-May 1923 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:42
  - New Mexico, Jun 1914 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:43
  - Ohio, 1912-1932 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:99
  - Oklahoma, 1933, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:100
  - Pennsylvania, 1904 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:101
  - Pennsylvania, Jul 1937-Aug 1937 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:102
  - Texas, Sep 1935 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:103
  - Wisconsin, Jan 1936-May 1936, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:104
  - Dues Book, 1926-1936 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:105
- SERIES III. NEW YORK STATE CORRESPONDENCE
  - New York State, Jul 1930 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:44
  - New York State, Jul 1931 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:45
  - New York State, Aug 1932 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:46
  - New York State, Erie County, Jun 1932 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:47
  - New York State Correspondence, Apr 1905 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:48
  - New York State, Jan 1934-Dec 1934, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:49
  - New York State, Jan 1935-Dec 1935, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:50
  - New York State Correspondence, Jan 1936-Aug 1936, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:51
  - New York State Correspondence, Jan 1936-Aug 1936, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - New York State Correspondence, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:52
- SERIES IV: NEW YORK CITY CORRESPONDENCE
  - New York City, Kings County, Sep 1908-Jul 1909, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:53
  - New York City, Feb 1911-Dec 1911, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:54
  - New York City, Jan 1912-Nov 1912, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:55
  - New York City, Bronx Agitation Committee, Jul 1912-Dec 1912 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:56
  - New York City, Feb 1913-Sep 1913 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:57
  - New York City, Nov 1915-Dec 1915 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:58
  - New York City, Jun 1916-Oct 1916 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:59
  - New York City, Minutes, 1916, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:60
  - New York City, Mar 1917, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:61
  - New York City, East Side Agitation Committee, Feb 1917-Oct 1917, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:62
  - New York City, Nov 1920, Jan 1921-Jun 1921 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:63
  - New York City, Mar 1923-Apr 1923 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:64
  - New York City, Apr 1923-Aug 1930 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:65
  - New York City, Mar 1931-Dec 1931, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:66
  - New York City, Jan 1932-Dec 1932, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:67
  - New York City, Jan 1933-Dec 1933, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:68
  - New York City, Furriers' Union Correspondence, Jun 1933-Jul 1933 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:69
  - New York City, Furriers' Union, Norman Thomas Correspondence, Jun 1933-Jul 1933 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:70
  - New York City, Furriers' Union, Norman Thomas Memorandum, Jun 1933 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:71
  - New York City Furriers' Union, Minutes, Jun 1933 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:72
  - New York City, Furriers' Union, Reports, Jun 1933 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:73
  - New York City, Women's Committee, Dec 1933 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:74
  - New York City, Jan 1934-Dec 1934, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Film R-7124, Reel 13, Frame IX:75
  - New York City, Women's Committee, May 1934-Dec 1934, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:76
  - New York City, August Claessens Correspondence, Jan 1935-Dec 1935, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:77
  - New York City, August Claessens Correspondence, Jan 1935-Dec 1935, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - New York City, August Claessens Correspondence, Jan 1935-Dec 1935, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - New York City, Julius Gerber Correspondence, Jan 1935-Dec 1935, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:78
  - New York City, Grievance Committee, 1935, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:79
  - New York City, Miscellaneous, Feb 1935-Dec 1935, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:80
  - New York City, Women's Committee, Jan 1935-Dec 1935, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:81
  - New York City, Women's Committee, Jan 1935-Dec 1935, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - New York City, Women's Committee, Jan 1935-Dec 1935, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - New York City, Women's Committee, Jan 1935-Dec 1935, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - New York City, YPSL Crisis, Mar 1935-Jun 1935, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:82
  - New York City, August Claessens Correspondence, Jan 1936-Dec 1936, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:83
  - New York City, August Claessens Correspondence, Jan 1936-Dec 1936, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - New York City, Julius Gerber Correspondence, Jan 1936-Dec 1936, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:84
  - New York City, Membership Lists, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:85
  - New York City, Membership Lists, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - New York City, Miscellaneous, Mar 1936-Jul 1936, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:86
  - New York City, Organization and Propaganda, Aug 1936-Nov 1936 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:87
  - New York City, Women's Committee, Jan 1936-Jun 1936, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:88
  - New York City, Women's Committee, Jan 1936-Jun 1936, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - New York City, Financial Papers, Jan 1937-Jun 1937, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:89
  - New York City, Mimeographed Reports, Apr 1937-Aug 1937, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:90
  - New York City, Women's Committee, Mar 1937 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:91
  - New York City, Mar 1939-Aug 1939, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:92
  - New York City, Dec 8, 1940, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:93
  - New York City, Apr 1941 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:94
  - New York City, Jun 1944 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:95
  - New York City, Jan 1945-May 1945 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:96
  - New York City, Apr 1946 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:97
  - New York City, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Film R-7124, Reel 14, Frame IX:98
- SERIES V: FRAGILE ORGINALS
  - FRAGILE ORIGINALS from BOX 1, FOLDER 1 through BOX 1, FOLDER 9 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - FRAGILE ORIGINALS from BOX 1, FOLDER 10 through BOX 1, FOLDER 17 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - FRAGILE ORIGINALS from BOX 1, FOLDER 18 through BOX 1, FOLDER 21 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - FRAGILE ORIGINALS from BOX 1, FOLDER 23 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - FRAGILE ORIGINALS from BOX 1, FOLDER 24 through BOX 1, FOLDER 27 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - FRAGILE ORIGINALS from BOX 2, FOLDER 1 through BOX 2, FOLDER 6 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - FRAGILE ORIGINALS from BOX 2, FOLDER 7 through BOX 2, FOLDER 15 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - FRAGILE ORIGINALS from BOX 2, FOLDER 21 through BOX 2, FOLDER 23 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - FRAGILE ORIGINALS from BOX 2, FOLDER 24 through BOX 2, FOLDER 26 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - FRAGILE ORIGINALS from BOX 3, FOLDER 1 through BOX 3, FOLDER 2 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - FRAGILE ORIGINALS from BOX 3, FOLDER 3 through BOX 3, FOLDER 8 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - FRAGILE ORIGINALS from BOX 3, FOLDER 9 through BOX 3, FOLDER 13 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - FRAGILE ORIGINALS from BOX 3, FOLDER 14 through BOX 3, FOLDER 15 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - FRAGILE ORIGINALS from BOX 3, FOLDER 16 through BOX 3, FOLDER 21 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - FRAGILE ORIGINALS from BOX 4, FOLDER 1 through BOX 4, FOLDER 2 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - FRAGILE ORIGINALS from BOX 4, FOLDER 4 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - FRAGILE ORIGINALS from BOX 4, FOLDER 5 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - FRAGILE ORIGINALS from BOX 4, FOLDER 6 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - FRAGILE ORIGINALS from BOX 4, FOLDER 7 through BOX 4, FOLDER 9 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - FRAGILE ORIGINALS from BOX 5, FOLDER 1 through BOX 5, FOLDER 2 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - FRAGILE ORIGINALS from BOX 5, FOLDER 3 through BOX 5, FOLDER 5 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - FRAGILE ORIGINALS from BOX 5, FOLDER 6 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - FRAGILE ORIGINALS from BOX 5, FOLDER 7 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - FRAGILE ORIGINALS from BOX 6, FOLDER 1 through BOX 6, FOLDER 2 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - FRAGILE ORIGINALS from BOX 6, FOLDER 3 through BOX 6, FOLDER 5 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - FRAGILE ORIGINALS from BOX 6, FOLDER 6 through BOX 7, FOLDER 1 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - FRAGILE ORIGINALS from BOX 7, FOLDER 2 through BOX 7, FOLDER 11 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - FRAGILE ORIGINALS from BOX 7, FOLDER 12 through BOX 7, FOLDER 16 (Box 11, Folder 3)